Let's welcome Mr. Sino from Substance
Hello everyone
Hello everyone, I'm Sino
I'm very happy to be here today
to share the process of clothing with the MD team
Today I'm mainly responsible for making the beautiful Punggol clothing
In Substance, I mainly do the material work
Today I'm going to show you the whole process of the clothing
There's a lot of repetitive content
I'll show you this part
You can see the skirt inside
and some of its processing methods
and the jacket
I'm not sure if you can tell
It's very professional
The waist and the leather
These three will cover some of the processes
and some of the characteristics
As for the whole process
just like Sherry said
it's as simple as the MD
Each material in this section
will not exceed two to three steps
This material
We'll get into the actual content of today
Because this will take a long time
The contents of the three parts I chose
are not interrupted
There may be some selection areas
and some sewing and pen brushing
It's easier to speed up during this time
All the processes are in an infinite process
You can see how I did it step by step
In terms of the material
We can see the substance in the inventory
In fact, the substance has another feature
If you are familiar with it
You should know that it is a parameterized text
Today I don't have time to show you
how to make a parameterized text
I'll show you all the materials
Let's start from the beginning
I'll share with you the important points
in the process
To choose from the inventory
I think it's in line with the theme
of this time
I chose four materials in total
The entire clothing
It uses these four leather fabrics
and some patterns
You can see in this material
It has some pre-painting
At the same time, you can go
to the line to adjust its parameterization
It can control some of them
Choose this leather
It means its color
And some of its old
Some of its folds
And so on
Can be controlled
I use this one
I can actually put my whole
These fabrics of leather
To cover it
I can adjust it to various kinds
This is still more convenient
There is a point
It's just a pity
I can't see you in time
when I'm sending it
There may be problems
I'll share it after I'm done
The whole
To see your questions
In the Q&A section
I'll try to answer as many as possible
Because I'm now
This broadcast
Sharing with live
There will be a delay of one to two minutes
OK
We can see this is the group
Some of our
Some lace
There are some
Just now
When we were on the tree
It has a lot of patterns
Then I will choose some
On the pattern
There will be some static content
OK
We can see it in Panther
Directly inside Panther
Directly used
This model is made
Its face
It's all double
This face is also very high
I also
But that UV
Is divided very much
It's very beautiful
The UV that comes out directly
It's very convenient
I made it directly
Then I will
On this technology
I didn't do too much top
More is to show the material process
You can use this model directly
Now
If you use a lot of friends
Can see
This is
Double
It's more convenient to use
I just saw that
Our
2D UV and 3D
It can be cut open
Cut open
Can drag
Different sizes
Then
Directly give it a
Model of a layout
Other
Other parts
It's all a process like this
You can see
You can see the left
It's divided
The parts above
Each of them I give
It's all 4K
Such a degree
That
The model of the role
Behind
You see the rendering
I just gave it a color
Then gave a
Just show
Gave a little
3S
Such an effect
Then
I give this clothes
A basic
Structure
But just drag
Adjust its
Tiling
Because it is a
Very basic
It may be
This kind of
Auto
Detail structure
Will affect some
Roughness
And some
Reflection
Some of these textures
Lay down
Below
OK
Then
At this time
Because the back
I want to do a processing
At this time
You can share it in advance
Then we can see
On this screen
Its clothes
The sleeves
And the middle
This part of the line
And
This
The main material of the clothes
The area
They are
Based on
This model
On the pull
In fact, I
On this
I did some
Some add-ons
Then
This
Add-on
It can
It can use
The height
To generate
The last
Some
Model details
Effect
To break down
Such a
Is an average
This concept
Then
I
Here
Add to it
I
Personally
Will get used to
I just used
This pattern
I will
Its color
Roughness
All
Remove
I will add
A layer
To control
Its color
Its
Other
Various
In this way
Will
This is personal
Habit
If
In this material
It will
Have some
Such
properties
Then you can
Adjust directly
In fact, on this pattern
You can already see
At this edge
I am very thin
Its UV
Will be larger
I will use it directly
Because
It is already horizontal
Very good
To do
At this time
Add a
New one
Layer
In
Its
This is
This color
On the layer
I just chose
Its height
To use
One
Procedural
This kind of
Fold
As a height
To add it
To it
To create
This kind of
I want
Its edge
It will have more
More details
More
Some
Beautiful
This kind of
Flower edge
Its
Because
Its sewing line
It will be pressed
Every layer
It has its
Some layers
This
In
It will be very convenient
To
To do
Then
Added
One
Then
Gave
A cover
Then
Here
As a
Choose
Because
Its model is
Overall
Model
At this time
It chooses
To make
It has different
Choose the face
Choose UV
With the model
Because it is connected together
I am here
Go to the manual
Pulled
Here
Repeat
and adjust the tiling of the working stream like this.
Let's take a look at the live stream.
Because there will be a delay, I will talk about the edge interaction later.
I will also do this, because this model
is actually recommended to do it with the back of the model.
The effect will be better, but you can also draw.
Because you can see that I can do this fold.
Oh, he just saw the message and missed one.
Then I will add blur to it here.
Blur is very sharp.
Then give it a blur and then adjust it.
Make it richer this time.
Of course, its height and those can be done as you want.
Yes, the thickness of the model will be better.
The effect will be better.
After all, it is a thin piece.
No matter how you do it, the angle and other aspects will not be good.
It will be curled.
It's not that good-looking.
This model has thickness and no thickness.
So when I use this to deal with that without thickness,
I will draw a little bit on the edge.
OK, the same operation.
Then I will go again.
I will choose again.
This one is cut open.
UV is cut open.
Then I choose the UV option.
That is the way to choose.
Then cut directly.
We can see that the UV will be selected directly.
This will be very fast.
Then in this kind of closed edge.
There will be clothes, there will be edges.
There is also a connection part in the middle of the sleeve.
Then I will also make a choice.
In summary.
If you look at it directly,
it is to make a selection area.
Then because this is what we are going to do.
It's not that kind of, it's not that kind of very old, very broken.
I didn't use too much of it here.
Ah, it's made of plastic.
Or plastic ball.
Then choose directly.
Use the materials we want to make.
Add it up.
Do some details we want.
I will wear a little bit of plastic on the belt at the back.
How to deal with such a large area.
Because it's dirty on this dress.
It doesn't look good.
Then this kind of fine edge.
Give it to him.
The details come out again.
In fact, if you want to add more.
This panel is very, very convenient.
But if we want to do it again.
Clothes design in this regard.
There are more of this.
Some of these pursuits and requirements.
Or design this piece.
That designer.
Still need to go more.
To do.
You can do some custom-made.
This kind of.
Is not affected.
OK.
I should come now.
To do the thickness.
In this piece.
We add a layer.
To give this layer itself.
One.
We can see a height.
Because it is pure.
I want it.
There is a point here.
How about.
I want it.
It's not to say that.
But I feel fascinating.
favorite this one everything.
This is just the same.
I asked you to tell the truth.
I have serious questions and give you an answer.
When you're this introduction.
Of the movie.
If this is my 산
Dare to.
To compromise is actually inside this microphone.
To increase the screen brightness.
I think.
Let me.
Just a bit.
Because this is not your egg.
I feel different.
OK.
No.
The first thought in this tool.
Have you seen it.
I'm not going to.
Don't put it in charge of you.
Is there a lot of money to do?
Yeah.
It is.
In the same way, I will clean up all the edges
to make it less flat.
SD will be more complicated than Panther,
but just like what Sherry said earlier,
once you understand the logic of the software,
it's still OK.
Now we can see the thickness.
In this process, if it's high or not full enough,
you can adjust the blur.
You can also add it on top of this.
You can add a Level layer to adjust its contrast
and its strength.
Here I added a little bit of speed
to see its range.
At this time, I should make the thickness of the edges.
What we just saw is the same logic.
I will draw some of it.
I will reduce the height of this layer
and add some blur to the edges.
When we zoom in,
it must be a blur.
After all, it's a thin layer.
When we zoom in,
we can see that it's a thin layer.
our light beam passes by its edge,
it will form a visual feedback
that turns like this.
This is one of the ways.
After we took a small one
and tested it,
it's still very convenient
to draw in the UV interface.
We just need to draw it with one stroke.
If it's a game,
I think it's okay.
Because I used to play games before.
The edge processing
may be like this.
It's almost done.
If it's going to the visual level,
it will definitely not be able to hold it.
We need to give it thickness.
If it's going to the visual level,
it will not be able to hold it.
So, we have divided these
into our main base text,
and I want to add some more
rich details.
So, at this point,
we have a part missing,
which is the seam line.
So, we add a gray line
and choose a seam line brush.
We can try it first.
It probably has the effect we want.
There are three types of seam line brushes.
Each seam line brush
has different kinds of seam lines.
You can choose the seam line
according to what you want.
I've adjusted the color.
I've tested the thickness
that I want.
After that,
we can choose the seam line
according to what we want.
It has to be lunch in this layer.
So, the layer is white.
The layer is black.
You can also change the layer.
You can change the layer
as well.
You can also adjust the layer
after you finish it.
as well.
We are going to adjust the layer
according to this layer.
If the details are still high, you can make a small groove in each part of the fabric to match the seam line.
In fact, this requires a lot of details.
We added the details of the seam line step by step.
Next, I want to add some dark lines.
For the dark lines, I didn't do roughness or reflection.
I just wanted to add some light and shadow on the toes.
Then, I added some details of the seam line.
Now, we can choose our own pattern.
In this case, I chose some patterns from the many channels.
Some of them have some parameters that can be adjusted.
I just need to give it a little bit of tiling to adjust it.
It doesn't take much time.
I only need one.
Semi-main.
and put it on top of the height value.
Okay, I'm done with this big body.
I want to see if the final effect is convenient for me to adjust.
Now, I will use Stager to help me observe the effect under the rendering.
Because Substance has a few software,
Stager is one of them for rendering.
It can be very silly to go in directly.
Because the Substance software is seamless.
Just like I sent it to Stager, it came in.
All the material effects came in.
Then I will set my light and shadow here.
I'll take a look at the effect I took.
Is it what I want?
Then I will be able to quickly adjust it in the back.
Then I will simply set its texture attribute.
Now it is under the default rendering effect.
Then the light track of the right corner will open.
It will see the real effect.
Then I will select my material.
After the material is selected, the texture attribute here is the same as that of PANTER.
Because it is easier for me to develop here.
This is for this kind of material.
It adds the attribute of this sim.
It's like a simulation of that kind of hair.
It's a reflection of that kind of light.
Then PANTER can also go directly to the new material ball and activate it directly.
Then it is the same here.
Set its material effect.
Then I will open its透.
This透 is not the kind of transparent channel.
You can understand that it is 3S.
It is the degree of transparency of the object itself.
Then I will adjust a大概 directly.
Because in the end, it will enter the light track effect.
Adjust a大概.
Then switch.
Let's take a look at some of its texture.
The intensity of the texture details.
And some of the various textures.
What is it like?
You can adjust it.
If you are slow, you can reduce its sampling value.
If you use GPU rendering, it will be faster.
This is the Stager.
It has designer, PANTER, Stager, sampler, these several.
I like using it because I can just click at PANTER,
and it comes to the Stager.
All of my material and documents are the same.
The standard model system.
I don't need to process it again.
Then I just need to come back and change it.
Look at it.
Then I have to adjust it, I will go back to the panel and adjust it, it can be synchronized very well with this side, we can see
Uh, roughly, because this is the second time I do it, the parameters should be almost the same, not too far away
Our, the effect of our line is similar to the feeling of sato, including some details of the structure of its texture
Uh, I think it's about time, I may have entered the next one, uh, let's come to this one
This part of the waistband, we can see that this is what we showed you on the inventory before
We chose this one
I also looked at it
You can see the complexity of its pattern
This is very easy to do in the designer
To duplicate this kind of
Then use this material directly
There will be several previews, including its pattern, and there are different previews like this
To switch
If you do it directly, you can make a pattern that you want
If you want to do it directly or directly, you can do it by mistake
The place where you can change the highlight
In the front, you can change the standard highlight
The background light for that stage, in fact, the demand is fine
The one-space K is that high
You can run it
It depends on the complexity of your scene
I see it as no problem running this kind of thing
Hey
Let's go on to adjust its uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh movements on Amon's card
So, I'm going to choose this and then I'm going to adjust its effect, can I see the stop, the performance, thetwo points, and the포 is perfect like this, right?
Because we can see that the colors on it are divided into a group and it is very good to adjust some of the colors I want.
Its roughness, because this material is built-in, it has a pre-made metal-to-metallic, and it has not been exposed.
So I don't want it to have such a strong metal attribute, so I gave it another one separately.
But when it comes to this, it is also relatively flexible.
I gave it a new layer separately.
I only keep the metal to make a stack with it to adjust it.
It's almost like this.
Then, like this, it's a big group.
Make a mark on this group and adjust it yourself in this group.
But it won't affect anything else.
Here, the whole UA is also selected.
Because its UA has been cut and broken, it will be very good.
It will be selected very quickly.
You can turn it off yourself.
There are actually a lot of fun things.
I can't give you a lot of opportunities later today.
The game process, the parameterized model can run.
Because it's not used much now.
The parameterized model is not used much in this process.
In the stager, you can run the parameterized model directly.
There's not much advertising here.
Let's get back to the topic.
Let's take a look.
Let me see if it's in the store now.
Oh, give this one in the middle.
I want it to be cloth.
I want it to feel like cloth.
That's very simple.
Give it a pattern.
Give it a very high tiling.
Make it feel like cloth.
Then adjust the roughness very low.
In this way, make a piece of leather.
It's that kind of block.
In this way, it will look better.
If you like painting, then in my understanding,
That's the color division.
You cut these to a different quality.
It will look better.
This model was originally made very beautifully.
Then I provided such a design opportunity.
Then it's very convenient to choose directly.
As for the edge, I will choose to use leather.
That's the whole body.
I will use that parameterized leather.
To adjust the effect of different workmanship.
According to its part.
Some parts may take a long time to mold.
I will make this leather look a little more mature.
As for this edge.
I will remove this fold.
Because I want it to be hard.
I want it to be hard.
Then it will look like a girl.
Like a real girl.
Like a pretty girl.
Don't be so bad.
In fact, this piece is the same as this edge.
Its thickness.
It's the same as that kind of dress.
Thank you.
I think I took all of your questions today.
It's difficult to summarize.
What do you think in terms of touch?
That's a fast program.
I think I will take it easy and give you a long explanation.
Here I am speaking for
a few minutes.
That's three minutes so to speak.
And then it's three and a half minutes.
we can also choose some of them that we didn't choose just now.
We can see that on the left side of the screen,
he brought it himself.
In this brush, he brought these and some pull chains, etc.
Adjust its size, its color.
After the sewing line is sewn,
because every time it is selected,
it may be re-colored.
It is recommended that when everyone does it,
we use the color below it in this project.
There is one in the lower left corner of the color board.
Save it.
In this way,
some of the colors used in the corresponding project
will be locked down.
It's convenient for us.
It's behind.
If you accidentally make a mess or something,
it's gone.
This is the same.
Go straight.
You can see that this line,
it will bring some holes in the middle of the line.
It will be more realistic to simulate.
Such as O2,
and so on.
It's still going down.
In fact,
as long as I pull a little bit,
I don't need to deal with other things too much.
There are some cases
where I can't see it.
If it is blocked,
it will directly go back to the UV layer.
Then I will pull it in this interface.
This will also be more convenient.
The model is the same.
I just made the material.
It doesn't affect the model section.
There is not much difference.
In the workflow,
it is only in the material section.
Then it will provide the service for this design area.
We have all kinds of sutures.
Then I choose this.
It should be considered as a particularly
evil suture effect.
There are a lot of sutures here.
The method is provided.
Then we add some details
that we want.
That's it.
There are a lot of problems.
Let me take a look.
I'm afraid to miss what I'm talking about.
If it's simple,
I'll reply to you right away.
If it's a little bit complicated,
we'll take a look later.
Let's take a look.
Now,
if I look at where I am now,
I can see that
I'm in the middle of the screen.
Then,
sometimes,
I can see it here.
Sometimes,
when I add a new layer,
I will find that the hair and the hair
are stacked together.
I don't want that.
In fact,
in the upper right corner just now,
switch to the corresponding layer.
Choose the way to add it.
You can remove it.
I'm going to do
that kind of little nail.
I'm going to choose
an original model like this.
Let's go directly.
Let's take a test
to do an effect first.
Then,
as for why to hit this nail,
I also checked some information
and then looked at some.
Others just like to hit it
because there are a lot of those nails.
So,
this is also pretty good.
this is also a way
to do this kind of small detail.
This is also a way to do this kind of small detail.
You can see
I will be on the top
with the same thickness as before.
I will choose a layer.
Then,
this layer
will directly adjust its height.
Then,
I'm going to control it
on the operation.
Are there any?
At the same time,
I'll save its
professors and officers
to adjust
the attribute
that can be adjusted.
It is OK
to make it come out
and image the picture.
So,
if you don't need
the real model
to stick out,
then this one
is supposed to be braided.
In fact,
this will be
possible to achieve such an effect.
At the same time,
In the same way, I will add another layer because it is directly placed on it, it is still a bit fake.
In the same way, if I use this, I will go in the same way.
We let this little hat stick out.
Then I will make a layer and press it down to make a effect like this.
This is the position.
Then I will make a blurry processing of this manufacturing.
It will have the effect of wrapping.
As for how much, you can adjust it according to your needs.
This is the new version. I forgot the date.
This is the current version.
OK.
In fact, the details of how much to do depends on the requirements of our project and personal works.
For example, I may have a lot of ways, different ways.
If I encounter it, I may use this to deal with it.
Including David Chang, he also has a lot of experience in SP.
From models to materials, there are also a lot of experiences.
There are a lot of experiences to share.
I am here to make a software.
Later, everyone will wait for David Chang to appear.
You guys are so detailed.
I want to see the version again.
David Chang is actually here.
Do you have any presentation?
Let's see what we're doing.
David Chang came out here last time.
I think it's cool what David Chang did last time.
He also shared.
You can learn from him.
for processing various materials.
Next, let me see where it is.
It's this piece of leather.
This piece of leather still uses the material just now.
The whole piece does not feel old.
I removed all the marks.
I will keep some marks for the joints of the shoes and gloves.
I will keep some marks for the shoes and gloves.
Now you can see that the model is divided into two parts.
I will select the model from the table.
I did not use the model.
I opened a layer separately.
I will use this color in the right process.
And here,
I will add a new color layer to it,
and give it a shader
to break the color of its large area.
At this time, I will use some noise or intelligent materials.
Then I will fill in a noise directly here.
You can adjust the tiling, adjust the water level,
and all kinds of things.
We can also slowly test the effect.
In this case, I will quickly adjust the tiling.
It is randomly distributed on the top.
Some of the tiling
cannot be kept completely the same color.
Especially the one that is often used with this kind of bend on the body
will add some very weak colors to it.
You don't need to draw it, just drag and drop one,
and then adjust it.
In fact, it is quite intuitive.
If you can't do it with Photoshop,
this is just a 3D file.
Then drag and drop this one.
Then here, I will add it.
It should be made of metal.
Let me take a look.
Oh, no, no, no, not metal yet.
I am giving it some kind of edge intelligent manufacturing.
It is actually using what we just saw,
the AEO crafted,
as well as some hair lines, space hair lines,
such information.
It will help us to calculate
which places it is blocked,
which places it is the edge.
Then through this,
we can see that in some places where its edges are blocked,
I can give it some more details of all kinds of things.
The same logic.
In fact, in any part,
we can do it according to our material.
If you want to make it old,
it is more convenient.
Then we will probably give it the edge
and add some edge effects.
Because the noise added just now
is still the whole surface.
It can't be refined to such a detailed place.
At this time,
I will also add some edge details like this.
So it is quite straightforward.
For example,
I have to make this one a bit wider.
Then I can put it in.
So it will be a bit wider.
But this is the same.
If you want to make it bigger,
you can make it a bit wider.
You can also make it shorter.
So if you want to make it a little wider,
you can make it a bit wider.
It can be a bit wider.
You can make it a little wider.
It is just a little bit wider.
It is not like this.
I think it is quite good.
It is just a little bit wider.
So I think it is ok.
We will continue to look at the other parts.
Do you have any other questions?
How do you feel about the AEO project?
No, I am satisfied.
Thank you.
I'll show you how to do it slowly.
You can do it on the model,
or you can do it on the 2D model as well.
Okay, let's go into the acceleration mode.
What are we going to do next?
Let's take a look.
Oh, it's metal.
There's still some metal on this part.
Let me show you.
Let's remove it.
After removing it,
I'm going to change its hair line and height.
I'm going to choose this small part.
Let's adjust the color.
Actually, it looks good.
Let's see how detailed we can make it.
Let's see.
Now, I'm going to cut the hair in the middle area.
Then we're going to get the part that's up to the head.
For this part,
we're going to cut the top.
If you cut the top like this,
you can see the hair is going to be cut,
then we're going to cut the bottom.
Now, we're going to cut the top.
Okay, it's looking good.
It's done.
Let's continue.
Because it's too small, it will look more obvious when you look at it from a larger angle.
When it's done, let's adjust some of its effects.
Let's adjust some of its effects.
Like we did earlier, we can adjust it to match its shape.
You can obviously see that we have the lightest area in the lens.
On certain points in the密 sample, that's good.
But because of its limited effect, Алsha selected one light spot toожд은
The lightest spot is sufficient.
.
I tried it a few times before.
OK, that also gives it a cover.
Use the cover to make a sound system.
We just tested it on that little fan.
Then we just use it.
It's the same, it's adjustment.
Adjust to the effect you want.
It's OK.
That's it.
The highest is 8K.
Usually it's 4K.
Including the one we downloaded.
The downloadable material ball provides such a attribute of 8K.
So, it can be used.
It can't be so absolute. It's too hard to use.
OK, then we...
Other components.
You can see that there will be a little bit of light on the shoulder armor.
I made some details on the rendering board.
It's also based on that logic.
But it's a flat surface after all.
So we want better results.
And some structural information.
The model should have a lot of models.
Make some details.
We can also use height to draw on it.
Unless you use an illusion.
Drawing is another story.
But most of the projects.
Whether it's a game.
Or a visualized case.
It's generally not that hard.
Because it's not...
It's more of a real-time interaction.
The same thing below.
It's integrated with that.
After we're done here.
We should be able to go to this area.
I'm done with this case.
Just like just now.
Directly to the left.
Send it to Stazer.
Activate its light.
It looks like this.
Then we can hit the camera.
And so on.
But now.
In the shader of Substance.
Actually.
You can draw directly in the panel.
3S.
It can output 3S channels.
This is the whole.
Complete.
The top.
Because it's too empty.
I drew the screws on top.
The gear is not a screw.
I drew some.
I drew some effects.
Finally adjusted.
Adjusted.
Its.
Actually.
Other processes are repeated.
Look at this skirt.
I choose a pattern that I just selected.
Then put it on.
Then dress.
Wait a minute.
Open each layer.
The first layer.
This is socks.
On the other side.
We can see.
Actually just one layer.
Then stack.
It's the same as what we did just now.
I stacked the fold details again.
Then finally let it sew.
So it came out.
You can.
You can even do some irregular damage on the edge.
There is no more.
A process.
This is the same as the operation principle just now.
The same fill out.
S.
This is a kind of seam.
A bit of a delay.
Then.
Finally.
That's it.
Because just now.
In order to follow this video.
The content was interrupted.
That's actually.
Sometimes.
Sometimes its shader.
From.
I saw the stager to the painter.
It's a new shader now.
This one here is 3s.
Or here.
OK.
Gain the
In fact, it's more convenient.
We used to be in the s3.
In the past.
Inside our game, most of the games.
Have the effect of edge light.
Now you can actually be in the center.
The edgings.
The range is so that the effect.
Directly output into post-its.
Which place is about what?
We didn't give too much content for this part.
The hair was adjusted with a grid line.
The face is not high, so there is no problem.
The other thing is that when everyone saw the rendering,
they gave a few cameras and then went to do the rendering.
You can see the Stager advertising time.
You can see the time to catch up on the left side.
The left side actually provides a model.
It can set up a scene inside.
The fun thing about using it is that it supports digitized models.
This is my second model.
After I set up my digitized model,
I can adjust it.
I can use a asset model to material to combine it into a scene.
I can verify it in this.
And then I can send it to Unreal, Unity, or other brands.
This is very convenient at the moment.
The future digitized designer's digitized model function
will slowly connect to the ones that everyone uses.
So please look forward to it.
OK.
That's all for today.
Thank you.
Thank you everyone.
It's a precious weekend.
It's not easy.
OK.
Next, Sherry, is there a Q&A?
Or what?
OK.
Let me take a look.
There is a Q&A.
Q&A session.
Wait a minute.
Can you see the previous chats?
Because I don't think there are as many chats as before.
I can see them.
Yes.
I was looking over there and over there.
I turned on the phone over there.
Do you have any questions about Substance, Painter, or Stager?
Now, please hurry up and ask.
We have about 10 minutes of Q&A time.
Because I was looking at both sides,
there might be some problems.
If you have any questions,
I didn't reply to them.
You can send them here.
The material of the Lei Shi Hua panel is the same.
I can use this time to open the document here.
You can see the ball in the background.
This is the material of a designer.
The material of the moon.
I personally think that SP is very convenient for all art designers.
You can draw in it very intuitively.
You can draw in it very efficiently.
You can use the material of this substance.
There are some tools to help you do it.
As for SD, we see that these intelligent materials,
including some of the ways we use in SP,
it will build our working methods and our intelligent materials at the bottom.
Yes.
Bosch, can you take a look at this?
Let's activate this.
The first time I opened it, it might be a little...
It might be a little slow.
The material of Bosch,
it was hollowed out in the middle.
This material is self-supporting the transparent channel.
I didn't make the thickness of Bosch,
because I was lazy.
I didn't make the thickness because I didn't show it to everyone.
The height here is...
The height...
The height of this edge is what we just did in SP.
When you finish it, if you need to change it,
the height speed can be restored.
Look at how I did the material.
I just pulled the material up.
You can use it.
Later, we can use it as a tool.
You can use it as a tool.
Later, Brother Qiang will talk about a lot of this kind of technology flow, which is very convenient for everyone to use in the public, and combine them together to make this material.
This time, I didn't show you how to make this material, and how the designer did it. It's actually set up. You can also get it online.
Embroidery
This time, I can't really talk about it.
The question is too big. My brain is a bit short.
How to learn SD to make it right?
I think SD is first of all to build up the knowledge.
Just...
This is the first one.
SD is a bit big on A3.
You can take a look at it in the material area.
Take a look at the master.
I learned SD...
I watched Daniel's...
I watched Daniel's tutorial when I first entered the industry.
It's still very good.
This is not an advertisement.
This is my personal learning process.
You can learn any software.
Especially now, the software is very fast.
New technologies are constantly overlapping.
Keep learning.
That's it.
There is no such thing as an official method or formula.
You can learn it.
If you want to make a back hole, there is no meaning.
One is like this.
I can see it.
Let me show it.
Let me show you that Panther to Stager.
Stager to Stager.
I'm making a small ball.
I'll take this one.
Because it's the Chinese New Year.
Here, on the left.
On the left, this place.
Click Send.
It'll come over.
So, this is my personal habit.
It's more...
Its material, text, and text are all here.
All of them are here.
And then,
Tender.
Tender, now, this material.
After selecting this material,
we can see its...
Its code.
And then,
these things, including 3S.
The properties of 3S.
It's almost all in here.
Let's take an example.
It's still the fabric.
First, in this material,
let's see.
I'll add a layer.
In here, I can...
Add its text.
These properties are activated.
After they're activated,
I'll add one.
Here.
Activate it.
You can do it.
After doing it, it will...
You have to export the map.
It's the same as those.
Just do it.
Now, we can see.
How many of them are in here?
3S.
So, let's see.
And then,
we have this.
3S.
You can see it now.
I'll put it over here.
I'll take a little one.
It's turned on.
This model,
the parameterization I just mentioned,
for example,
Wes also shared how to do this parameterization model.
You can see this model
can be adjusted.
I also did some
game-like parameterization cases before.
You can see it
in the substance
public account.
It can be changed in various ways.
Including some...
This sofa is a little fun.
It's just a default
with some...
Stager, sampler,
these are the personal versions.
It will log into Steam.
If you want to subscribe for a long time,
the official version still has it.
Look at that.
This is a little fun.
Is there any time left?
Let's do a broadcast.
We talked about
the game-like process.
This is how I use it.
You can see that we go to customize assets.
We all know
that the designer
is in the model,
in the material,
the spreadability.
If we do a similar asset in our project,
before,
we can go to the same one.
The same asset,
but we can also
customize it.
If we go to the model,
we can customize it.
There are different ways.
We can customize it
in different ways.
Let's go to the next one.
The next one is
the machine.
This is what
the machine looks like.
I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
What's the reason?
I don't know either.
I don't usually get stuck.
I use a laptop to run.
You guys are a little hot.
Yes, the sound is not lagging.
Only the picture is pretty good.
The light is still good.
It's really good.
This is not a joke.
Look at Panker's face just now.
Panker was thinking the same thing.
It's all high-pitched.
It's normal.
I'm using a real card.
If I quit,
my laptop will be broken.
I can't even...
I can't even do that.
I can't even quit.
It's okay, you can keep teaching.
There's no screen.
What are you talking about?
Just now,
you saw how IMP adjusts the length
of the card.
Actually,
now,
if we combine some materials,
we can make some small ones.
The big ones are still limited.
I'll try to customize the small ones.
For example,
plants,
public buildings,
houses,
and some factories.
Let me share the screen first.
Let me see.
I have a question.
Just now,
when I turned on the camera,
you laughed at the tiger.
You talked about embroidery.
I can use this new case
to share with you.
I hope it won't happen again.
Because it's the new year.
Now,
we can see
the material
problem.
Let me try
it again.
This is the model
I've chosen.
You can see
what it looks like
in the stager.
Its body.
Because it's the year of the tiger,
I made this.
It's a bit confusing.
You can see
here.
The individuality.
Coat.
The second layer.
Highlight.
The color properties.
You can choose
what you want.
This embroidery
is made by SD.
I'll show you the layers later.
This is the fabric.
It needs
seam.
Let's add seam.
Let's go back to this pattern.
I'll turn it over.
Actually,
it's better to combine the two sides.
It's more convenient for me.
As for this part,
I made the whole pattern
in designer.
I added it in SP.
I added some small details like this.
This is its
seam line.
And this is
its connection.
I haven't finished the bottom yet.
This is the connection.
What is this layer for?
Oh, the butt.
After finishing,
we can see this layer.
We can add another layer.
Let's turn it off.
We can see the seam color.
Hmm?
Let's add this layer.
Then we can add this.
And we can add this.
Okay.
It's a bit awkward.
This is the look.
Let me find it.
It's not like this at all.
Let me try this first.
Oh, I'm too nervous.
The software is normal. I forgot to activate it.
Here it is.
We found it.
Yes, yes, yes, the system didn't open.
After activating the system,
this effect came out.
I'll go back later.
The boss deducted my salary.
Let's adjust the color of the red cloth.
Let's adjust its edge effect.
After it's done, I'll send it.
I'll send it now.
OK.
Let me refresh it.
It's awkward again.
When it comes to SD embroidery,
I see that...
My approach is...
I just saw a very funny tiger.
It's painted black on it.
Actually, I did the positioning.
I did some things in SD.
I made this needlework.
I made this fabric.
I made the pattern.
I made a drawing of the area according to my positioning.
The area.
I'm going to...
This area is probably...
How does the needlework go?
Its direction, its density.
To match it.
Then I added some details like this.
Then I turned it over and did...
Add some more details to my hand.
I created a new layer here.
As you can see,
it won't be so funny this time.
Send it to the stage.
OK.
I'm going to...
I'm going to check my hand.
OK.
Actually, all the designs are really quite nice.
Actually, it's not...
It's so...
It's not as obvious as you think.
So I don't want to...
I really want to...
I just wanted to see if it's...
I'm not sure.
As you can see,
the angle of my hand is not exactly...
That's why I'm not sure.
I don't know a lot about the direction.
I want to try...
Let me see.
Now let me see if this is correct.
Yes.
I don't know the angle.
When I see it,
it's not that obvious.
It's to our advantage.
You can see it.
Maybe if you...
It has already wrapped up this kind of edge.
The axis is made by SD.
If you want to make an axis, there are several ways. If you are like me,
it is worth it. In fact, there is no axis. You can make it in this area.
Another way is to use Tile simple, and cut it.
There should be a lot of tutorial cases in Tilesimple.
Tile simple allows you to connect to an entry for a normal connect source.
You do an area construction
. If you want it to turn,
you can use a connecting
method from the tip of the道.
It would be easier to understand this, but
It will follow the direction of your hair.
This is a way to control the direction of the thread of the embroidery.
We can see that because I cut it here,
sometimes I can't recognize it at once.
This is the effect I did in SP.
I changed it to another color.
You can see what that is.
You can see that the hair on the edge of the comb is in a slender state.
You can also change the height here.
Let's take a look at the actual place just now.
We don't want it to fall down or climb up.
I still put it in.
OK.
I put it in the IMB.
I put it in this.
I set it to this.
This is just a case to show you
what it can do in a fast way.
Let me give it a material first.
It's convenient for us to see the material change.
When the model changes, the material changes.
Let's find a skin.
OK.
This is the place where the model goes to.
Let's see its state.
We can switch some of its previews.
This preview is done in advance.
It is equivalent to this asset.
We need to control the changes in its parameters.
That is the tutorial of SDA materials.
There should be a lot of business on it.
I saw a lot of great SDA tutorials.
As for the materials, let me take a look.
If you want to learn SDA, there is a personal learning method.
You can see the materials in the inventory.
It has SBAs.
You can download it directly.
You can download the SBAs that you like and want to learn.
You can open it.
All the shortcuts are in it.
You can take your time to look at it.
You can take your time to try it.
It is very easy.
That is the most standard file.
You can quickly...
You can quickly understand what it looks like.
What is it like?
International.
Yes, this is a completely...
This is a very good SDA.
Then you see its...
I want to adjust its width.
It is no longer...
It is no longer pulling it out.
It is based on the number of our asset specifications.
Then this kind of change happens.
If I have a game...
I have a project.
I need this kind of...
This kind of asset.
I can give the project such a sofa.
I have a good budget.
Then I have a different room.
Then I put it down.
Then I adjust the parameters.
I put this product in front of me.
Then I can find it directly.
This will be very convenient.
Then group sofa, single sofa,
double sofa.
It's all possible.
Oh, it's gone.
Oh, my God.
This is still different from Houdini.
I personally will not compare this with Houdini.
Houdini has its own strong point.
Then I use the designer.
The whole designer is actually...
Sometimes it's just...
More of a parameterization.
It's around the bottom layer.
Designer.
It's a parameterization concept.
That includes its model.
It's also here to serve this process.
Then we can see it.
After the model is added in,
Combine with the material.
It can be on the asset.
Do some fun parameterization.
Such a kind of...
Oh...
A little bit of delay.
Yes.
Then I put that...
The time is almost up.
Let me see how it works.
There was no setting before.
It didn't fall.
It didn't fall out.
It fell out.
Let me see.
It didn't fall out.
I haven't finished.
My bell isn't ringing.
Let's see.
It doesn't work.
It's the Lunar New Year.
It's preparing for the Lunar New Year.
I'll just open this one.
Oops, I'm done.
I'm so embarrassed.
I forgot to find the channel.
I'll just put it back.
I can't find it.
It's not because my English is good.
My English is terrible.
I'm used to it.
I'm not used to it.
This isn't an anti-earthquake.
My English is really difficult.
I found it.
Oh, height.
In here,
I can see the effect of its switch.
I'll adjust its parameters.
And then I can set it directly to its corresponding model
and give it a score.
You can see its...
Okay.
This is how you can see it.
Let's look at it again.
You can see that the edge of it is a real line.
Because it is not a completely protruding object.
Let's go back to the top again.
Let's look at our yearbook.
Let's use this to wish everyone a happy new year.
Okay, happy new year.
Yes, happy new year.
Let me take a look.
VR modeling.
I think everyone can play with it.
Modeler.
It will be officially released next year.
Everyone can play with it.
Modeler has one feature.
In fact, it still has a long way to go.
This is objective.
But it has a very interesting thing.
In other words, in addition to VR, it can also be used for computers.
Its integration.
Its integration is that we no longer need to merge it together.
The model itself will be connected to it.
Its face will not collapse.
And I can easily make some kind of interface.
There are also some things like this.
Like this.
You have to brush up the details.
And then you can go in and collect it.
You know.
Its integration is a little interesting.
My language ability is a little bad.
It's hard to express.
It should be publicized next year.
Everyone can play with it.
Yes.
Okay.
Thank you again.
Thank you for your time today.
And patience.
If there is a chance in the future,
we will have more discussions.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Xinlong.
No.
No, no.
No counseling for everyone.
Then how can I turn it off
Begone from me, brother.
OK.
If you leave me here directly,
I will leave.
OK.
Right.
And if everybody wants to know more about the teacher later,
you can search Xino on artstation.
Yes.
You can find our hip teacher.
Bye bye, bye bye, bye bye, bye bye
Okay, okay, thank you
I can't turn it off, can you help me turn it off?
Okay, okay
Okay
Okay, then we'll see you at 5 o'clock
See you at CINO
CINO
Okay, if you want to go to the bathroom, you can go to the bathroom first
After that, it's our...
That...
It's Qiang's part
Don't, don't, don't
This part of the draw has already ended
You don't need to refresh the chat after that
After that, the last draw is that there will be a table at the back of the stage
I'll announce it to everyone later
Okay, okay, okay
Everyone, take a break first
I'll go call Qiang
Oh, by the way, everyone must remember to scan the QR code
Because the last grand prize is
From the person who scanned the QR code
The person who filled out the questionnaire
They started to calculate
So everyone remember to scan the QR code
And it's solid
We watched it
And then
We can measure them
It's gonna be fun
Thanks
Thank you
One more time
So there are already values
We compared for that
To the questions we took